TODAY'S LUNCH
I'M HEADING BACK NOW.
THE TEA FROM TODAY'S MEETING
HAD A STALK FLOATING UPRIGHT.
SO
I'LL SEND YOU LUCK, TOO
LUCKY
Senpai.
Someone's in a good mood.
Were you chatting with
Kamegawa or something?
H-How did you know?
I wonder how.
Seems like you're getting along
with Kamegawa-kun.
Do you really think so?
Am I wrong?
Well, how do I put this...
He's the first friend I've made, so...
I'm being a good friend... right?
Why are you laughing?!
Sorry, don't mind us.
Oh, come on!
By the way, Senpai,
his birthday is next month, right?
Are you going to celebrate it?
That!
About that!
I do want to celebrate it.
But I've never celebrated someone's
birthday before, so I don't know what to do.
Oh...
Then how about we celebrate it
during the group birthday party?
You know, the one we do at
the beginning of every month?
We hold a party for all the staff
with birthdays that month.
I could use that!
I owe you one, Kankaiji!
So that means you'll give
Kamegawa something, right?
You know, a P-R-E-S-E-N-T.
A p-present...
They're taking too long.
But she seems to be having fun.
I mean, yeah,
they went from a senior-and-junior
relationship to friends.
There's no doubt they've made progress.
But also, it's obvious
that they like each other.
Why can't they be self-aware about that?
Hmm...
At the very least, Kannawa isn't aware.
Agreed.
Well...
I wonder how this is going to turn out.
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
EPISODE 11:
WE'RE GONNA CELEBRATE YER BIRTHDAY TO THE FULLEST!
"We're Gonna Celebrate
Yer Birthday to the Fullest!"
Yeah! The group birthday party!
You heard from general affairs, right?
Are you going?
I'd like to go, yes.
Would you like to go together, Senpai?
Of course I'll attend.
I'm going to celebrate it to
the fullest, so be prepared!
Okay. I'll prepare myself.
A-All right.
Uh... Want to grab lunch today?
There's... something I want to ask you.
Understood.
Good. Later, then.
Oh! Hello, Kamegawa-kun the "friend"!
Ugh. What do you want?
You and Senpai seemed
to be having a good time.
G-Got a problem with that?
Not at all.
But I do wonder if you're okay
keeping things like this.
What do you mean?
Let's all do our best today.
Today's special is good.
Y-Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
What was it you wanted to ask me?
Huh?! Er, well...
Well, you see... my cousin's friend's...
little sister's neighbor's
big sister confided in me...
and I need your advice!
That's quite a distant relationship you have.
So what did she discuss with you?
Sh-She wants to know...
what kinds of gifts men like
to get from women.
I see.
I wonder what...
Huh?!
I'm sorry.
I never really thought about that myself.
I-I see.
Th-Then... wh-what about you?
Huh?
What would you like to get as a gift?
If it were me...
Since it's gotten colder,
maybe a pair of gloves?
Gloves?
If I were to buy gloves, what's his size?
Senpai?! What's wrong?!
There are so many gloves to choose from.
I forgot to ask if there were any
specific materials or colors he'd prefer.
You're sure struggling over
buying a single pair of gloves.
Shaddap!
How about we ask an employee
for recommendations?
You're right. Yeah.
But also, I bet you want to take this
opportunity to choose a pair on your own.
Yeah! But...
Sorry. I'm not confident about this.
This is my first time
choosing a gift for someone.
I'm worried I'll pick something weird.
Your birthday's next week, right, Miki-chan?
We should have a birthday party!
Really? Thanks!
Let's invite everyone!
I'm so happy!
Oh, but I don't really like Azusa-chan.
I get it. She's scary.
I feel like she'd bring a weird present.
Yeah.
What are you saying?
You're friends with Kamegawa-kun now, right?
I like to think so, but...
I don't know if he'll like my choice or not.
Hey.
Don't you think anyone who doesn't like
what a friend gets them isn't really a friend?
Even if it's something they don't want,
they should be happy just to receive it.
That's what I believe.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Okay!
Touch.
Thank you!
Good morning.
Cute.
What's up?
Yu, your birthday's next month, right?
What do you want for your present?
Ah, forget it. I'm scared about
what you'll want in return.
What do you mean?
Oh! Are you going on a
birthday date with Kannawa-san?
N-No way!
What?
But I think my company's having a party,
so she might celebrate with me then.
Hmm.
Just so you know, nobody likes a suck-up.
What? Since when was I one?
You don't remember?
Your birthday party from way back.
Happy birthday!
Th-Thanks.
Hey, so whose present was the best?
U-Um...
I liked everyone's!
Forget it!
Huh?
Back then...
I had no other choice but to say that.
I get that.
But if you're nice to everyone,
someone ends up getting hurt instead.
You're right.
What?
We need to keep it a secret
from Kamegawa that you're
helping out with the birthday party?
It's not exactly a secret...
but there's no need to tell him about it.
This is something I decided on my own.
I don't want him to feel guilty
about it or anything.
How commendable...
Good work!
You two must be hungry.
I bought some hot pork buns and snacks.
Pork buns!
Yippee!
Since the birthday party's in two days,
we need to put in one last push.
It won't be easy, but let's do our best.
Yeah!
Where would you like to go for lunch today?
Sorry. I've got things to do,
so can we go another time?
Oh... Sure.
Be sure to eat real food!
Y-Yes, ma'am.
For tomorrow's birthday party,
Kannawa-san from the publicity department
is part of the volunteer staff, right?
Yeah. She said she wants to help
and she's willing to do anything.
Really? That's out of character.
I wonder what brought
about that change of heart.
LIST OF BIRTH MONTH PARTICIPANTS
YU KAMEGAWA
Looking good.
Yeah. Looks like we'll manage
to get it done today.
Oh, by the way,
I brought the list of birthday people.
Wanna see?
Yeah.
Usa-san from general affairs
has a birthday, too.
We were in her care when we were first hired.
She told us where to find cheap
apartments near the company.
Do you know what Usa-san likes?
Fried chicken, salted fermented
seafood, and apple pie?
Do you think we can add those
to tomorrow's catering?
What?
Even the fermented fish?
I'm going to make a call.
Oh, my...
This is...
You're kidding me...
C-Can we make it in time if we redo it tonight?
Yes, we'll make it work.
Sorry, Kannawa.
I really want to help, but I've got
a company dinner tonight of all nights.
M-Me, too. I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Huh?
I'm the one who spilled the paint.
I'll handle this on my own.
Don't worry about me.
You two can go to your dinners.
Senpai...
Really, I forgot you can be like this.
There's fifteen minutes left for lunch.
We can help out as much as we can.
Yeah!
Okay.
Good work today.
Should we head home soon, too?
No. I'm going to stay behind
to work on the project—
O-Overtime! I'm working overtime!
Did something happen?
I can lend a hand.
What?
I can't let you do that!
H-Having my junior help with overtime...
That's out of the question!
Just go home already.
Hurry and eat your dinner,
take a bath, and sleep!
Got it?
Then... I'll be heading out first.
Good work today.
All right. I got this.
What are you doing?
Y-You!
D-D-D-Didn't you go home?!
I forgot my train pass on my desk.
When I went to get it, I noticed this was
the only room with the light left on.
So... is this...
D-Don't look!
Sorry.
It's nothing, really!
I already saw the whole thing.
Could this be for tomorrow's...
Yeah.
I thought so.
So this is why you've been busy, huh?
I'll help you.
What?
H-Hold on a minute.
I've never heard of someone doing
prep for their own birthday party.
I just need to paint with this, right?
What an interesting design.
Actually, I spilled the paint on it.
I've been struggling with how to fix it.
Really?
I think this could work as-is.
Really? It works?
I haven't done anything like this
since my school festivals.
It sure is fun.
Senpai, your cheek.
Huh?
Use this.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
I'll come home with a cake.
Uh-huh. Love you, too.
I'll be home soon, so wait for me!
W-We did it.
We did.
For tomorrow...
I do want to celebrate your big day.
But I hope the others enjoy it, as well.
I'll make sure of it.
I'm sure they'll like it.
Uh-huh.
Happy birthday!
This ain't good.
I'm so excited, I can't sleep.
Thanks to Kamegawa, we finished the sign,
but I still have the mission
to give him his gift...
I'm sure they'll like it.
The birthday party feels fancier this month.
I heard Kannawa-san was part of the
volunteer staff and put in a lot of work.
Wait, really? That's out of character for her.
Hey.
P-Pick whichever one you like.
Kannawa-senpai!
Good work today!
I'll gladly take one!
You know, Senpai did all this for you.
Yeah. She told me.
Huh? Really?
Senpai's just awkward. That's all.
She's actually nicer than anyone.
She's a warm-hearted person.
I want other people to know that about her.
Agreed.
Though, are you saying that
because you're her friend?
Huh?
Thank you so much for throwing
such a great birthday party for us!
General affairs can do great things
sometimes, too, you know.
Nonsense. We're always
in your care, Hamawaki-san.
Oh, come on.
By the way, that sign looks amazing!
Was it handmade?
Huh? Well, I guess.
Wow! As expected of you!
Wanna take a pic of it?
Sounds good!
Please excuse us, then!
Yup. Later.
Anything else I can help with?
Nope! Don't worry about anything else.
Just enjoy yourself.
Are you sure?
Isn't that something we
need to carry over there?
It looks like it could be a lot. I'll do it.
Where do you want it?
I said—
Ouch...
Senpai!
Are you hurt?
N-No...
Are you okay?!
Yeah, nothing to worry about.
Wait!
Huh?
MEETING ROOM
FIRST-AID KIT
Please take better care of yourself.
But... she was in danger back there...
Yes, but I mean that you should
be careful all the time.
At my welcome party,
you drank alcohol in my stead, too.
What?
And you tried to work overtime
during a typhoon.
You handed out flyers in the heat.
That was the best thing to do at the time...
Even yesterday.
You were planning to finish
that sign all by yourself, right?
That would have taken you all night.
Please, don't push yourself too far.
I refuse!
Of course I need to push myself!
I'm just happy to be able to celebrate!
After all, today's your...
my... precious friend's birthday.
A friend, huh?
I...
Kannawa? You okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Um, sorry about before.
Thank you.
No worries. I'm glad you're okay.
Everyone's waiting for the star of the show.
Of course!
Sorry. Let's go!
Yes, ma'am!
What? Are you nervous?
Happy birthday!
This'll be on the company news board!
Smile, everyone!
Say cheese!
Looks good!
Thanks, everyone!
I'm such an idiot.
Happy birthday!
Th-Thank you very much.
I have something, too!
Here!
Me, too!
Kamegawa-kun's popularity is amazing.
Maybe I shouldn't give him a gift.
Huh?! What are you saying?
But they're still talking.
Those who get up there are the winners here!
R-Really?
You want to see Kamegawa-kun's
happy face, right?
Um, well... yeah...
Um...
M-My junior...
Five... Just five minutes.
I'm sure you all want to talk to him, but...
Five minutes...
May I please borrow him for five minutes?
Of course you can!
So sorry to keep him!
Let's go!
What?
Sorry. Thank you.
Senpai...
Here! For yer birthday.
Thank you very much.
Can I open it?
Paw pads!
Wh-What do you think?
I didn't know what you'd like,
so I asked, and ya said gloves...
Wait, so that time...
Well... I picked somethin' that'll suit...
I mean, it was cute... I thought.
But it's somethin' more to my taste...
I-If ya don't like it, then...
Nope.
I really like them!
Thank you so much.
I'm glad.
Oh. But you got a lot of presents
from all these people today.
So I guess I should have gotten
something better after all...
I like them. Really.
I got a lot of things today, but...
this gift from you makes
me especially happy.
S-Sorry!
It's okay.
Before... you said you wanted
to be friends, but...
Hm? Something the matter?
My feelings for you...
are not just friendship.
What?